<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WinFellow - Amiga Emulator for Windows</title>
    <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WinFellow - Amiga Emulator for Windows</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 05:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 06:43:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/about/</guid>
      <description>Amiga Emulator for Windows Description WinFellow is a high performance Amiga Emulator primarily targeted for Windows. Its distinguished API and core do however allow a fairly easy port to other operating systems.
WinFellow is distributed under the terms of the GNU General Public License version 2.0 (GPLv2).
This site is WinFellow&amp;rsquo;s development home on GitHub.
The latest stable release can be found in WinFellow&amp;rsquo;s former home at SourceForge; the latest one published on SourceForge is v0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the team</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 05:43:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/team/</guid>
      <description> team member Petter Schau Torsten Enderling Worfje occupation programmer from Norway virtual desktop engineer from Germany engineer from the Netherlands tasks various beta team managerGitHub Pages/hugo website administration cross platform development modules emulation core RetroPlatform integrationhardfile/file systemdebuggersystem information graphicssoundGUI email petschau@gmail.com torsten.enderling@gmail.com worfje@gmx.net </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contacting us</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 05:45:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please check the FAQ that can be found in WinFellow&amp;rsquo;s User Manual before contacting us, it is usually the fastest way to find a solution to your problem.
There is a WinFellow specific support forum at the English Amiga Board, which is also monitored by us.
You could also make use of the GitHub issue tracker.
Any comments on how to improve WinFellow are welcome!
You can also contact us directly by sending an email composed in English language to Torsten Enderling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contributing</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 05:45:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/contributing/</guid>
      <description>WinFellow is developed by a team of volunteers in their spare time; you are very welcome to make contributions of your own. Contributions can be improvements to the code, new features, but can also include documentation updates or whatever else you feel could be an improvement. It is best if you find something you want to work on rather than mailing us and ask to be assigned a task. Since WinFellow is developed on an idealistic basis, the basic idea is that everyone should do something they like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinFellow v0.5.9 RC-1 released</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2023-09-03-winfellow-v0.5.9-rc-1-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 05:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2023-09-03-winfellow-v0.5.9-rc-1-released/</guid>
      <description>There is a new release candidate build of WinFellow hosted in the GitHub releases section. Compared to the earlier version 0.5.8, the following changes are included in this build:
System requirement changes
support for Windows XP and Vista has been removed; version 0.5.8 will be the last WinFellow release to support Windows XP or Windows Vista. This enables us to take advantage of enhancements in the toolset used during development and testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinFellow v0.5.8 released</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2019-07-12-winfellow-v0.5.8-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 05:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2019-07-12-winfellow-v0.5.8-released/</guid>
      <description>There is a new public release of WinFellow v0.5.8 in the GitHub releases section; it had been published earlier as release candidate 1.
Compared to the earlier version 0.5.7, the following changes are included in this build:
New features
support for RDB hardfiles was implemented; while creating a new hardfile from the WinFellow GUI still creates &amp;ldquo;plain&amp;rdquo; hardfiles, a Rigid Disk Block can be created using tools like HD Toolbox the default naming scheme for filesystem devices has been changed from DHx: to FSx: to avoid naming conflicts with existing RDB hardfiles a 64 bit build is now provided; the NSIS installer will install either the 32 or 64 bit version depending on the operating system that is used Bug fixes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinFellow v0.5.7 released</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2018-01-02-winfellow-v0.5.7-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2018-01-02-winfellow-v0.5.7-released/</guid>
      <description>Bug fixes:
floppy code was updated to use a track limit &amp;gt; 80; it will output random data beyond track 80 - fixes Outrun/The Games: Summer Edition; also added missing checks for disabled drives, fixing Winter Olympics 94 fixed a bug where unexpected pixel format flags besides RGB stopped DirectDraw initialization several bugs in the screenshot code were fixed; standalone screenshots were not saved correctly in D3D mode, and used with Amiga Forever raw screenshots were missing screen areas due to faulty initialization of the internal clipping areas fixed screen area mismatch when Amiga Forever region/size settings are both set to auto; auto clipping is still not supported CPU instruction fixes: fixed a signed bug in 64-bit division minor timing adjustment for btst CIA event counter changes according to documentation the project files were updated to Visual Studio 2017 Please see the included file ChangeLog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinFellow v0.5.6 released</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2017-11-12-winfellow-v0.5.6-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2017-11-12-winfellow-v0.5.6-released/</guid>
      <description>New features:
Amiga Forever 2017 support modules were updated to the latest version, improving Amiga Forever input device handling by reducing lag Bug Fixes:
improve support for IPF images (align disk words to sync if sync is found on an odd boundary) Please see the included file ChangeLog.txt for a full list of changes, including minor bug fixes which are not listed above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinFellow v0.5.4 released</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2017-03-11-winfellow-v0.5.4-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2017-03-11-winfellow-v0.5.4-released/</guid>
      <description>New features:
re-designed display settings to make use of modern higher resolution displays more intuitive; instead of configuring a window resolution, scaling and overscan area can be configured automatically to create a window of the optimal size and scaling factor; both can also be configured manually to arrive at frequently window sizes support for the Direct3D 11 graphics API; this requires DirectX 11 to be installed on Windows Vista, the platform update KB971644 should be installed, as it contains required updates to DirectX the graphics card has to provide hardware acceleration for Direct3D ability to save screenshots to the pictures folder (hit &amp;lt; Print Screen &amp;gt; to trigger) support for automatic, as well as 3x and 4x scaling, which is useful for 4K/high DPI displays; for the best results, try leaving the scaling at automatic very basic serial port/UART emulation; nothing can be connected to the serial port; this is mostly used for serial debug logging (which is active only in debug builds of WinFellow), but the port is always being emulated Bug Fixes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinFellow has a new home</title>
      <link>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2016-01-11-winfellow-has-a-new-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 06:43:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://petschau.github.io/WinFellow/post/2016-01-11-winfellow-has-a-new-home/</guid>
      <description>WinFellow development has found a new home on GitHub; please update your bookmarks accordingly.
Downloads for older releases are still available at SourceForge for reference; for future news and updates, please visit us here.
The GitHub source code repository is available here.
Future releases of WinFellow will be published in GitHub&amp;rsquo;s releases section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
